So the point that Gemini is developed by Google makes it more powerful, and even having
an unfair competitive advantage, if that makes sense.
Because when it comes to Google, we have a long list of products that belong to Google,
so we have a list of Google products over here as you see.
So Google has a lot of products, right? A lot of the products that you use daily, you know,
blogger, Gmail, what else, YouTube, I don't know, Google Docs, Google Slides, all those
Google Docs editors, the search engine itself, you know, recapture, you know, all these weird
names that you may not even been thinking that Google owns them, but Google does, you know.
Android is owned by Google, this is a very big advantage. Chrome is owned by Google, this very
browser that we're using, and there are a lot of products to the company, right?
And these products come together and create an ecosystem that is called the Google ecosystem.
And the point here is that when it comes to activities, and when it comes to things that are
related to this ecosystem, Gemini performs way better than the other chatbots.